const questions = {
    zh: [
        {
            question: "新郎＆新娘喜歡的飲食風格？",
            answers: ["清淡", "重口味", "愛吃甜", "愛吃辣"],
            correctAnswer: 0,
        },
        {
            question: "新郎＆新娘在一起多久？",
            answers: ["3年", "4年", "5年", "6年"],
            correctAnswer: 2,
        },
        {
            question: "新郎＆新娘在哪裡認識的？",
            answers: ["夢裡", "花蓮", "台北", "交友軟體"],
            correctAnswer: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "誰先跟對方說我愛你？",
            answers: ["新郎", "新娘", "同時", "重沒說過"],
            correctAnswer: 0,
        },
        {
            question: "新郎在哪裡跟新娘求婚？",
            answers: ["床上", "車上", "花蓮三仙台", "台北景觀餐廳"],
            correctAnswer: 2,
        },
        {
            question: "新郎在哪裡長大？",
            answers: ["美國", "加拿大", "烏克蘭", "南非"],
            correctAnswer: 3,
        },
        {
            question: "新郎＆新娘養的寵物貓咪叫什麼名字？",
            answers: ["小可愛", "爺", "寶貝", "咪咪"],
            correctAnswer: 3,
        },
        {
            question: "新郎跟新娘誰比較會唱歌？",
            answers: ["新娘", "新郎", "都一樣難聽", "都一樣好聽"],
            correctAnswer: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "早上起來對對方說的第一句話或是動作？",
            answers: ["早安寶貝", "我出門了", "Kiss", "喂咪咪了嗎？"],
            correctAnswer: 3,
        },
        {
            question: "兩人出遊誰比較會規劃？",
            answers: ["都不規劃，說走就走", "新娘", "新郎", "兩人共同分工"],
            correctAnswer: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "新郎＆新娘最常一起去哪逛逛？",
            answers: ["寵物店", "新竹巨城", "全聯", "夜市"],
            correctAnswer: 2,
        },
    ],
    en: [
        {
            question: "What are bride and groom's preferred taste in food？",
            answers: ["Light", "Salty", "Sweet", "Spicy"],
            correctAnswer: 0,
        },
        {
            question: "How long have they been together?",
            answers: ["3 years", "4 years", "5 years", "6 years"],
            correctAnswer: 2,
        },
        {
            question: "Where did they first met?",
            answers: ["In their dreams", "Taipei", "Hualien", "Tinder"],
            correctAnswer: 1,
        },
        {
            question: 'Where said "I love you" first?',
            answers: ["Groom", "Bride", "Same time", "Never"],
            correctAnswer: 0,
        },
        {
            question: "Where did the groom propose?",
            answers: [
                "In the bedroom",
                "In the car",
                "Hualien - Sanxiantai",
                "Taipei michelin star restaurant",
            ],
            correctAnswer: 2,
        },
        {
            question: "Where did the groom grow up?",
            answers: ["America", "South Africa", "Ukraine", "Canada"],
            correctAnswer: 3,
        },
        {
            question: "They recently adopted a cat, what did they name it?",
            answers: ["Cutie", "Ye", "Baby", "Mimi"],
            correctAnswer: 3,
        },
        {
            question: "Who sings better between the groom and the bride?",
            answers: ["Bride", "Groom", "Both sounds bad", "Both are good"],
            correctAnswer: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "The first thing they say or do in the morning",
            answers: [
                "Good morning babe",
                "I'm off to work",
                "Kiss",
                "Did you feed the cat?",
            ],
            correctAnswer: 3,
        },
        {
            question:
                "When they go on a vacation who does the majority of the planning",
            answers: [
                "No planning, spontaneous adventures",
                "Bride",
                "Groom",
                "Both put equal amount of effort",
            ],
            correctAnswer: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "Where do they like to go shopping?",
            answers: ["Pet store", "Hsinchu Big City", "Carrefour", "Nightmarket"],
            correctAnswer: 2,
        },
    ],
};

export default questions;
